// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [

    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which of the following is a server-side Java Script object?",
        answer: "File",
        options: [
        "File",
        "Functions",
        "FileUpload",
        "Date"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "IsNaN() Evaluates And Argument To Determine if Given Value:",
        answer: "Is Not a Number",
        options: [
            "Is Not a Null",
            "Is Not a Number",
            "Is Not a New Object",
            "None Of The Above"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Function is Used To Parse a String To Int:",
        answer: "Int.Parse",
        options: [
            "Integer.Parse",
            "Int.Parse",
            "Parse.Int",
            "None Of The Above"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Method Prompt() Contain ........Number of Parameters.",
        answer: "Two",
        options: [
            "One",
            "Two",
            "Three",
            "Zerp"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Event is Used To Check An Empty Text Box:",
        answer: "OnBlur()",
        options: [
            "OnClick()",
            "OnFocus()",
            "OnBlur()",
            "None"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "GetMonth() returns The Month as:",
        answer: "Int",
        options: [
            "Int",
            "Char",
            "Float",
            "String"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which Of The Dialog Box Display a Message And a Data Entry Field?",
        answer: "Prompt()",
        options: [
            "Alert()",
            "Prompt()",
            "Confirm()",
            "Msg()"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 8,
        question: " ___________ JavaScript is also called client-side JavaScript",
        answer: "Navigator ",
        options: [
            "Microsoft",
            "Navigator ",
            "LiveWire",
            "Native"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "How does Java Script store dates in objects of Date type?",
        answer: "The number of milliseconds since January 1st, 1970",
        options: [
            "The number of days since January 1st, 1900",
            "The number of seconds since January 1st, 1970",
            "The number of picoseconds since January 1st, 1970",
            "The number of milliseconds since January 1st, 1970"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What is the alternate name for Java script?",
        answer: "ECMAScript ",
        options: [
            "Pathname",
            "LimeScript",
            "ECMAScript ",
            "None Of The Above "
        ]
    },
];